<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Jaipur Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Discover</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="tab_text_3">Hotels</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Exit</string>
    <string name="image_description">Place Picture</string>
    <string name="place_name">Place Name</string>
    <string name="place_description">Place Description</string>
    <string name="ratings">5.0</string>

    <string name="amber_fort">Amber Fort</string>
    <string name="amber_fort_details">Built By Raja Man Singh I. It is blending both Hindu and Rajput elements. With its large ramparts, series of gates and cobbled paths, the fort overlooks the Maota Lake, at its forefront.</string>
    <string name="hawa_mahal">Hawa Mahal</string>
    <string name="hawa_mahal_details">Built in 1799 by Maharaja Sawai Prathap Singh. It most recognisable monument in Jaipur. It is constructed of red and pink sand stones. Hawa mahal build with small windows and balconies.</string>
    <string name="city_palace">City Palace</string>
    <string name="city_palace_details">Maharaja Sawai Jai Singh built this monument in the 17th century, right in the heart of the pink city. It is a combination of gardens and courtyards, along with a blissful blend of Mughal, Rajput, and European architecture.</string>
    <string name="jantar_mantar">Jantar Mantar Observatory</string>
    <string name="jantar_mantar_details">The observatory houses several mind-blowing astronomical devices to make accurate astronomical calculations.This UNESCO World Heritage Site was built in 1738.</string>
    <string name="jal_mahal">Jal Mahal</string>
    <string name="jal_mahal_details">Or Water Palace, is located on the Man Sagar Lake. The building majestically rises amidst the water body and is surrounded by the Nahargarh Hills.</string>
    <string name="birla_mandir">Birla Mandir</string>
    <string name="birla_mandir_details">It is famous for its splendor, the renowned industrialist family of Birlas had constructed the temple in 1988.Dedicated to Lord Vishnu and Goddess Lakshmi, it is also known as Lakshmi Narayan Temple.</string>
    <string name="jaigarh_fort">Jaigarh Fort</string>
    <string name="jaigarh_fort_details">Jaipur has architectural brilliance in plentiful.Standing proudly amidst the Aravalli range, atop ‘Cheel ka Teela’ hill, the fort offers views of the Maota Lake and Amber Fort. It was constructed under the rule of Maharaja Sawai Jai Singh II in 1726.</string>
    <string name="chokhi_dhani">Chokhi Dhani</string>
    <string name="chokhi_dhani_details">Located 20 km from the city of Jaipur captures the rural life and essence of simple living with the Rajasthani culture very beautifully. It is nice place to eat, check Restaurant Tab.</string>
    <string name="albert_hall_museum">Albert Hall Museum</string>
    <string name="albert_hall_museum_details">Located very close to the Zoological Garden, the Albert Hall museum is a popular landmark in the city. Situated inside the premises of Ram Niwas Garden, it was opened to the general public in 1887.</string>
    <string name="rambhag_palace">Rambhag Palace</string>
    <string name="rambhag_palace_details">Originally built in 1835, Rambagh Palace has stepped gracefully through many royal transitions—from the home of the queen’s favourite handmaiden, to royal guesthouse and hunting lodge, and later as the residence of the Maharaja Sawai Man Singh II and his queen, Maharani Gayatri Devi. Today, this jewel in the Taj’s crown offers 78 stunningly restored grand luxury rooms and suites which were the chambers of the former Maharaja.</string>
    <string name="samode_haveli">Samode Haveli</string>
    <string name="samode_haveli_details">An urban oasis in the historic walled city of Jaipur, Samode Haveli is a traditional Indian mansion set in a verdant garden with apartments arranged around a series of intimate couryards. Built 175 years ago as a residence of the rulers of Samode, it is still occupied by their descendants, who have converted their home into a luxury hotel.</string>
    <string name="umaid_mahal">Umaid Mahal</string>
    <string name="umaid_mahal_details">One of the most classic Jaipur Hotels welcomes you to the world of traditional Rajasthani hospitality in this pink city Jaipur. Forget your worries in this beautiful and comfortable mini castle whose warm hospitality and splendor will linger in your minds forever.</string>
    <string name="jal_mahal_palce">Jal Mahal Palace</string>
    <string name="jal_mahal_palce_details">Built in 1745, the Jai Mahal Palace is a stunning piece of Rajasthan’s heritage, a great example of Indo-Saracenic architecture set amidst 18 acres of landscaped Mughal gardens. Jai Mahal Palace has been the residence of three Prime Ministers of the princely state of Jaipur. Painstakingly restored and recently refurbished, it is now a luxury five-star Taj heritage hotel equipped with all modern-day comforts.</string>
    <string name="shahpura_house">Shahpura House</string>
    <string name="shahpura_house_details">This hotel is a perfect escape for tourists who wish to explore the city in its truest sense. Well-furnished with modern amenities, the hotel offers a roof-top restaurant, a pool-side restaurant, a bar and a host of other facilities. To make your experience even better, they arrange multiple excursions and entertaining programs arranged for the guests.</string>
    <string name="mandawa_haveli">Mandawa Haveli</string>
    <string name="mandawa_haveli_details">A beautiful hotel with an decidedly “Jaipur charm”, Mandawa Haveli is worth every penny. Apart from a plethora of excellent facilities, the hotel also offers grand evenings with folk performances, puppet shows, and rooftop candlelit dinners. The antique décor keeps the Rajasthani spirit alive, and makes the stay even more worthwhile.</string>
    <string name="hotel_park_ocean">Hotel Park Ocean</string>
    <string name="hotel_park_ocean_details">If you are planning to visit Jaipur in near future and questing for budget 3 star hotel in center of Jaipur to make your visit a memorable one.then Book Hotel Park Ocean for Weddings, Parties and other events near Jhotwara road Jaipur. Get best priced Banquet halls near Sikar Road for various functions.</string>
    <string name="hotel_glitz">Hotel Glitz</string>
    <string name="hotel_glitz_details">Offering traditional architecture with modern amenities, Hotel Glitz is a super affordable option that you should consider. Perfect for both business and leisure, this hotel provides a range of services like spa/beauty salon, palmist and astrologer sessions, sightseeing tours, doctor-on-call, and a great multicuisine restaurant, to name a few. With a view of the city, this hotel provides a comfortable stay for all guests.</string>
    <string name="chokhi_dhani_food">Chokhi Dhani</string>
    <string name="chokhi_dhani_food_details">Has 59 cottages, 33 royal cottages, 8 Haveli Suits, 4 Conferences Halls, Ethnic and Multicuisine Restaurants, Outdoor Barbeque, Chandi Mahal Bar, Rhun Jhun- Discotheque cum Bar, Kesariya- The Sansha Spa all in Rajasthani village culture.</string>
    <string name="virasat_restaurant">Virasat Restaurant</string>
    <string name="virasat_restaurant_details">Virasat represents the real form of rajasthan. With rajasthan speciality thali and serve food in 24 carrot gold plate.</string>
    <string name="pride_amber_vilas">Pride Amber Vilas</string>
    <string name="pride_amber_vilas_details">Pride Ambervilas, an ethnic luxury hotel, located at prime location in Jaipur at a distance of 6 Kms from the Airport. Our resort is counted as the best properties in Jaipur for our dedication and obedience towards our guests.</string>
    <string name="kabab_and_curry">Kabab and Curry (KCCO)</string>
    <string name="kabab_and_curry_details">Kebabs and Curries Company (KC CO.) is a chain of Indian restaurants and eating joints elegantly combining creativity and authenticity of world famous Indian Kebabs and curries.</string>
    <string name="sethi_tikka_kabab_curry">Sethi Tikka Kabab and Curry</string>
    <string name="sethi_tikka_kabab_curry_details">Their Tandoori dishes are particularly delicious and intriguing. Must haves: Kadhai Chicken and Egg Curry.</string>
    <string name="sahu_chai_ki_thadi">Sahu Chai ki Thadi</string>
    <string name="sahu_chai_ki_thadi_details">One of the famous street food sharing jaipur\'s taste, culture and amazing street food.</string>
    <string name="rawat_misthan_bhandar">Rawat Misthan Bhandar</string>
    <string name="rawat_misthan_bhandar_details">Must try Pyaaz Kachori!</string>
    <string name="bapu_nagar">Bapu Nagar</string>
    <string name="bapu_nagar_details">Must try Sanjay Omelette!</string>
    <string name="lassiwala_mi_road">Lassiwala (MI Road)</string>
    <string name="lassiwala_mi_road_details">Must try Lassi!</string>
    <string name="saras_parlor">Saras Parlor</string>
    <string name="saras_parlor_details">Must try Crisp Pakodas and Delectable Jalebis!</string>
    <string name="bapu_bazar">Bapu Bazar</string>
    <string name="bapu_bazar_details">Must try  Kulfi Falooda- A winning Combination!</string>
    <string name="near_birla_mandir">Near Birla Mandir</string>
    <string name="near_birla_mandir_details">Must try Pav Bhaji at Pandit\’s!</string>
    <string name="falhaar_saraogi_mansion">Falhaar Saraogi Mansion</string>
    <string name="falhaar_saraogi_mansion_details">Must try Shrikhand!</string>
    <string name="laxmi_misthan_bhandar">Laxmi Misthan Bhandar</string>
    <string name="laxmi_misthan_bhandar_details">Must try Rabri Ghevar!</string>
    <string name="murli_paan_bhandar">Murli Paan Bhandar, in Tonk Road</string>
    <string name="murli_paan_bhandar_details">Must try Finishing off- Paan!</string>
</resources>
